ourkidsmom.com 2013-03-01

# Disclosure & Privacy - OurKidsMom

This policy is valid from 26 April 2010 

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact Heather (ourkidsmom at gmail dot com). 

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. 

The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog. All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network. Those advertisements will be identified as paid advertisements. 

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question. 

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest. 

To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org

_**PRIVACY POLICY:**_

This policy is valid from April 26, 2010

[OurKidsMom](http://www.ourkidsmom.com/) respects your privacy.

OurKidsMom and its affiliates may use cookies to store information about your preferences and other information. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and OurKidsMom does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers. Some advertising partners may use cookies. Some of the partners include, but not limited to [Groupon](http://www.groupon.com/), Ebates and AdBrite. OurKidsMom is not responsible for information obtained from affiliates.

OurKidsMom is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

OurKidsMom may on occasion ask for personal information, such as for giveaways. This information will not be sold or used for any purpose other than  contacting the winner of the giveaway. Your information may be sent to giveaway providers for mailing the giveaway. OurKidsMom is not responsible for information shared with giveaway sponsors as a means of mailing a giveaway. It is the intent of OurKidsMom that this information be collected for confirming winners of a giveaway as a method of prize distribution only.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

[contact-form] [contact-field label="Name" type="name" required="true" /] [contact-field label="Email" type="email" required="true" /] [contact-field label="Website" type="url" /] [contact-field label="Comment" type="textarea" required="true" /] [/contact-form] 

Be Sociable, Please Share!
